There's a group of men called The Firm.
有一群人叫 "公司"
They've been running things for a long, long time.
他们已经经营了很长很长的时间
And when they need someone to clean up their mess...
当他们需要有人帮他们收拾烂摊子时..
...They send me.
...他们就派我去
Go get your helmet. Let's go to the store.
去拿你的头盔 我们去商店
You look so cute, Nit.
你看起来真可爱 尼特
-Sam. -Nathan.
-萨姆 -内森
-Where are you -At home. Sewing.
-你在哪儿 -在家做针线活
Meet me at the diner.
在餐厅等我
Why?
为什么
How much trouble am I in?
我惹了多大的麻烦
An extra scoop for my favorite client.
给我最喜欢的客户多加一勺
Thanks, Rose.
谢谢 罗斯
I put in an extra scoop for my favorite client.
我给我最喜欢的客户多放了一勺
-Thanks, Rose, -I'm sure she won't be long.
-谢谢 罗斯 -我相信她不会太久的
You clearly don't know my mother very well.
你显然不太了解我母亲
Hey, stranger.
嘿 陌生人
-Can I lighten your load -Not carrying today, Rose.
-我可以帮你减轻负担吗 -今天不行 罗斯
There's a first time for everything. She's over there.
凡事都有第一次 她就在那边
Thanks for keeping an eye on her.
谢谢你照看她
You said you'd be here in 30 minutes.
你说过30分钟后到的
I'm a few minutes late.
我迟到了几分钟
Three hours.
三个小时
You're bleeding.
你在流血
Just another day at the office. Did you bring it?
又是在办公室的一天 你带来了吗
Anna May sure can pick them.
安娜 · 梅肯定能挑中它们
-It's loaded. -Good girl.
-子弹上膛了 -好姑娘
Listen, I, um... have to disappear for a while.
听着 我... 我得消失一段时间
-Then I'm coming with you. -You can't. Not this time.
-那我跟你一起去 -这次不行
Nathan will be here soon. He'll take care of you when I'm gone.
内森很快就会来了 我不在的时候他会照顾你
-I don't want to go with Nathan. -I'm doing this for your own good.
-我不想跟内森走 -我这么做是为了你好
I'll stay in the library with Anna May and the others.
我会和安娜梅还有其他人呆在图书馆里
It's too dangerous.
太危险了
What's going on?
发生什么事了？
It's... it's complicated.
这... 这很复杂
Tell me.
告诉我
I'm not a kid any more.
我不再是个孩子了
No, you're not.
不 你不是
You haven't touched your milkshake.
你还没碰你的奶昔呢
Didn't want to drink it without you.
我不想在没有你的情况下喝它
How long will you be gone?
你要离开多久
I have to make a quick phone call.
我得打个电话
Stay here.
待在这儿
Evening, gentlemen. Can I lighten your load?
晚上好 先生们 我能减轻你的负担吗
-Get lost. -Hey.
-滚开  -嘿
Hello, little girl.
你好 小女孩
Mommy says I'm not allowed to talk to strangers.
妈妈说我不能和陌生人说话
This "Mommy" looks a lot like you.
这个“妈妈”看起来很像你
Only bigger and more stabby.
只是个头更大 而且更爱捅人
Got my father's blood all over her.
她身上沾满了我父亲的血
I don't like you.
我不喜欢你
Enough games.
游戏玩够了
Where is she?
她在哪儿
Go kiss a pig.
去亲一头猪
Tell me where she is.
告诉我她在哪儿
Close your eyes, baby girl.
闭上眼睛 宝贝
Mom!
妈妈
♪ Yesterday ♪
昨天
♪ Any way you made it was just fine ♪
♪无论怎样你都做得很好♪
♪ So you turn your days into nighttime ♪
所以你把你的日子变成了夜晚
♪ Didn't you know ♪
♪你不知道吗
♪ You can't make it Without ever even trying ♪
♪你不可能不去尝试就做到
♪ And something's on your mind Isn't it ♪
你在想什么是不是
♪ Let these times... ♪
让这些时刻...
Evening, darling.
晚上好 亲爱的
-Can I lighten your load -I'm clean.
-我能帮你减轻负担吗 -我很干净
Regular clean or diner clean?
常规清洁还是餐厅清洁
-Forgot about this one. -Of course, sugar.
-忘了这个吧 -当然 甜心
-Yeah. -Yeah.
-是啊 -是啊
Boy.
孩子
Oh, these girls are worse than the Stasi.
这些女孩比史塔西还糟糕
You hurt?
你受伤了吗
Just another day at the office.
又是办公室的一天
Wow, you sound just like your mother.
哇 你说话真像你妈妈
I don't have a mother.
我没有妈妈
Well, you sure have her temper.
你的脾气真像她
What the hell happened tonight?
今晚到底发生了什么？
Bad intel.
糟糕的情报
You said four or five idiots with peashooters.
你说的是四五个拿着玩具枪的白痴
Yes. And?
是的 然后呢
Oh, for Christ's sake, child.
哦 看在上帝的份上 孩子
This was supposed to be low -profile, not a bloody massacre.
这应该是低调的 而不是血腥的屠杀
Next time, I'll just let them shoot me.
下次 我就让他们杀了我
Next time, just do what you're told.
下次 照我说的做
Remember who you're working for. As long as they're happy...
记住你为谁工作 只要他们开心..
You called me here oh -so -urgently just to remind me of that?
你这么急叫我过来就是为了提醒我这个
No.
不是
Your talents are needed, pronto.
我们需要你的才能 马上
Somebody stole from us.
有人偷了我们的东西
Who's crazy enough to steal from The Firm?
谁会疯到去偷公司的东西
Somebody who doesn't know who we really are.
一个不知道我们真实身份的人
An accountant. From the clean side of the business.
一个会计 干干净净的生意
How much did he take?
他拿了多少钱？
Enough to earn a visit from you.
足够让你去拜访了
We need that money back.
我们需要拿回那笔钱
Good girl.
好姑娘
I'll text you the address later.
我一会儿把地址发给你
Oh, and get rid of those stone -age firearms you carry.
对了 把你随身携带的那些石器时代的武器都扔掉
-I've had them for years. -Find an open vendor.
-我已经有好几年了 -找到一个开放的供应商
And get yourself some clean boomsticks.
再给自己弄点干净的嘣嘣棒
We can't have you linked to that war zone you left behind, can we?
我们不能把你和你留下的战区联系起来 对吧
Did you know about this little endeavor my son had on the side?
你知道我儿子在外面做的这个小生意吗？
Sorry, Uncle. I had no idea.
对不起 叔叔 我不知道
Where's the shoe?
鞋子呢
What shoe?
什么鞋?
The shoe that is not currently covering my son's left foot.
目前没有覆盖我儿子左脚的鞋
The one that looks like the right one.
就是那个看起来很像的那个
That fucking shoe.
那只该死的鞋
-I don't know. -Well, find it.
-我不知道 -那就找出来
Found it, Mr. McAlester.
找到了 麦卡利斯特先生
Nobody tells his mother about this.
没有人会把这件事告诉他的母亲
We'll tell her he ran off with some girl.
我们会告诉她他和某个女孩私奔了
I get it.
我明白了
Now, bring me the heads of the men that killed my boy.
现在 把杀死我儿子的人的头给我拿来
Hmm.
嗯
Hello, dear.
你好 亲爱的
What can I do for you?
我能为你做什么
I need to exchange some... books.
我需要换一些... 书
Well, that's nice.
真不错
Not a lot of people your age read nowadays.
现在你这个年纪的人读书的人不多了
-Do you have a card with us -No.
-你有名片吗 -没有
I'd like to open one.
我想开一张
Wonderful.
很好
What kind of... books are you interested in?
你对什么类型的......书感兴趣？
Mostly smaller ones.
大多是小型的
A few heavies.
有几本很重的
Well, you won't find them there.
你在那里找不到的
Those are our children's sections.
那些是我们的儿童区
The Enchanted Forest...
魔法森林
and The Never -Ending Ocean.
和永无止境的海洋
They sound like fun.
他们听起来很有趣
Have we met before?
我们以前见过吗
You seem so... familiar.
你看起来很眼熟
I'm embarrassed to say it's been a while since I visited a library.
我不好意思地说 我已经有一段时间没有去图书馆了
Well, that's no way to live, dear.
亲爱的 这可不是生活的方式
Let's get you into a good book.
让我们给你找一本好书
Come.
来吧
Anna May, this lovely young lady wants to open an account with us.
安娜 · 梅 这位可爱的小姐想在我们这儿开个户头
Well,
好吧
Madeleine should have told you that we don't accept new readers
玛德琳应该告诉你 我们不接受
without a reference.
没有推荐信的新读者
Madeleine had a hunch.
马德琳有一种预感
Fudge your hunches, if you pardon my French.
如果你不介意我说法语的话 请原谅我的直觉
-Technically not French. -Always literal.
-严格来说不是法语 -总是字面意思
-Yes, I'm literary. I'm a librarian. -Be that as it may.
-是的 我是文学家 我是图书管理员 -尽管如此
Florence, dear.
佛罗伦萨 亲爱的
Would you join us?
你愿意加入我们吗
I'm afraid we need a tie -breaker.
恐怕我们需要一个决胜局
Madeleine thinks this girl needs to do some reading.
玛德琳认为这个女孩需要读点书
I told you I had a hunch.
我告诉过你我有预感
There's something very familiar about her.
她身上有种非常熟悉的东西
Hunch, smunch.
预感 穆斯林
I, on the other hand, think we should dispose of the body
另一方面 我认为我们应该把尸体处理掉
and then have a long talk about our onboarding protocols.
然后好好谈谈我们的入职协议
You know I can hear you, right?
你知道我能听见你说话吧
Hush, girl.
安静 姑娘
Don't be rude.
别那么粗鲁
Turn around, hon.
转过去 亲爱的
And take off your hat.
把帽子摘下来
What did you say your name was?
你说你叫什么来着
She didn't.
她没说
Hmm. That's odd.
嗯 真奇怪
Well, girl?
怎么样 姑娘
Cat got your tongue Speak up.
怎么不说话了 大声点
It's Sam.
是山姆
Scarlet's kid.
斯嘉丽的孩子
Yeah.
是的
I knew it. Never forget those eyes.
我就知道 别忘了那双眼睛
We haven't seen you since you were yea high.
自从你上高中后我们就再也没见过你了
How is your mother?
你妈妈怎么样了
Haven't seen her in 15 years.
15年没见过她了
Well, that's something we both have in common.
这是我们俩的共同点
My, my, my. Little Sam.
我的 我的 我的 小萨姆
We hear about you all the time.
我们经常听说你
You've made quite a reputation for yourself.
你已经声名远扬了
Come here. Give Auntie Madeleine a hug.
过来 给玛德琳阿姨一个拥抱
Why come back now?
为什么现在回来
I needed clean guns...
我需要干净的枪
and I guess I needed an excuse.
我想我需要一个借口
Nice collection.
不错的收藏
And you take good care of them.
你要好好照顾他们
Let me guess. You're the sentimental type.
让我猜猜 你是那种多愁善感的人
Ro -man -tique.
罗曼蒂克
Sentimental types don't last long doing this.
多愁善感的人做这个不会持续很久
So, no. I don't think I'm the sentimental type.
所以 不 我不认为我是那种多愁善感的人
Tommy Tomahawk.
汤米 · 托默霍克
I looked everywhere for him.
我到处找他
Yeah, sorry about that.
是啊 很抱歉
So...
所以..
you're an idealist.
你是个理想主义者
Nope. Maybe I don't have a type.
没有 也许我没有固定的类型
Everybody has a type.
每个人都有自己喜欢的类型
-Everybody. -Mm -hmm.
-所有人 -嗯哼
Maybe I'm the professional type?
也许我是专业型的？
Ah. Old school.
老派
"No women, no children" type.
“没有女人 没有孩子”的类型
Women are fair game.
女人是公平的猎物
Gender equality.
性别平等
Very progressive.
非常进步
She's a feminist.
她是个女权主义者
Fine.
好吧
You get to live.
你可以活下去
We'll make these disappear
我们会让这些消失
and get you into some new, clean books.
让你进入一些新的 干净的书籍
You'll need a Jane Austen.
你需要一个简 · 奥斯汀
A Charlotte Brontë.
夏洛特·勃朗特
And a Virginia Woolf.
还有弗吉尼亚 · 伍尔夫
Oh, and an Agatha Christie.
还有阿加莎 · 克里斯蒂
For reading.
为了阅读
Please.
求你了
I need to answer this.
我得回答这个问题
You need to walk away and thank God I'm not in a killing mood.
你应该走开感谢上帝我没有杀人的心情
I got no choice.
我别无选择
-No! -Enough!
-不! -够了
Playing hard to get?
欲擒故纵
Not very smart, moron.
这可不明智 白痴
Not unless you want me to send your little princess back in pieces.
除非你想让我把你的小公主撕成碎片送回去
You have exactly 60 minutes
你有整整60分钟的时间
to bring the money to the Gutterball bowling alley.
把钱带到 Gutterball 保龄球馆
A minute late, and she'll be celebrating
晚一分钟 她就要和虫子们
her ninth birthday with the worms.
庆祝她的九岁生日了
60 minutes.
60分钟
Please.
求你了
It's my daughter.
是我女儿
♪ Yesterday ♪
昨天
♪ Any way you made it was just fine ♪
♪无论你怎么做都很好♪
Fuck me.
我操
♪ Try to remember ♪
努力记住♪
♪ The kind of September ♪
那种九月音乐
I'll get the doctor.
我去叫医生
Guns go in the cookie jar.
枪是放在饼干罐里的
-Hey. Haven't seen you in a while. -Hmm.
-嘿 有阵子没见你了 -嗯
And you brought a new friend.
你还带了个新朋友
-What the hell happened -I happened.
-到底发生了什么 -我...
Just fix him.
把他治好就行
I need him on his feet in ten minutes.
我要他在十分钟内站起来
Ooh.
哦
He's not going anywhere.
他哪儿也去不了
Not in ten minutes.
十分钟内不行
Maybe not ever.
也许永远不会
-So what can we do -"We"?
-我们能做什么 -“我们”
Well, you can start by not shooting people.
你可以从不开枪开始
Please. My Emily.
求你了 我的艾米丽
-There's no time. -Shh.
-没时间了 -嘘
Just relax. Take it in deep.
放松 深呼吸
Is that laughing gas?
那是笑气吗
Well, duh.
好吧 废话
Just patch him up.
给他包扎一下
I'll be back soon.
我很快就回来
He'd better be functional.
他最好能恢复正常
She's quite annoying, isn't she?
她很烦人 是不是
Who am I talking to?
我在和谁说话 被她
The guy that she shot in the stomach?
射中肚子的那个人
-Is it done -There's a change of plan.
-搞定了吗 -计划有变
What are you talking about What does that mean?
你在说什么 那是什么意思
They kidnapped his little girl. That's why he stole the money.
他们绑架了他的小女儿 这就是他偷钱的原因
If I'm not at the Gutterball in 15 minutes, they'll kill her.
如果我15分钟内不到 Gutterball 他们会杀了她
Sam, you're not thinking straight. Just bring the money back, now!
山姆 你没有想清楚 现在就把钱拿回来
I just need half an hour. I'll release her and bring the money.
我只需要半个小时 我会放了她 然后把钱带来
Okay. Listen to me, Sam.
好的 听我说 山姆
If you screw this one up, they will give the kill order.
如果你搞砸了 他们就会下令杀了你
And I won't be able to stop them.
我也无法阻止他们
She's just a little girl.
她只是个小女孩
I can't leave her to die.
我不能让她死
-I'm sorry. -Don't you dare hang up on me.
-对不起 -你敢挂我电话
-I'm sorry. -Don't you...
-对不起 -你敢..
Fuck.
操
Go to the Gutterball. Try to reason with her.
去找流浪汉 试着跟她讲道理
Bring back the money.
把钱带回来
Wait.
等等
Now, when I say "reason with her,"
现在 当我说“和她讲道理”
I mean no guns, no knives.
我的意思是不要用枪 不要用刀
She comes back alive.
她活着回来了
-Understood -Yeah.
-明白吗 -明白
And for God's sake...
看在上帝的份上..
be careful.
小心点
Remember who you're dealing with.
记住你在和谁打交道
What are you waiting for Go.
你还在等什么 快走
One of the men Sam killed was Jim McAlester's son.
山姆杀死的其中一个人是吉姆 · 麦卡莱斯特的儿子
Are you sure it was McAlester's kid?
你确定是麦卡莱斯特的孩子吗
Yes.
是的
The board is on its way.
董事会已经在路上了
Goddammit, Sam.
该死的 山姆
Who the fuck are you?
你他妈的是谁
Just someone who has your money.
只是一个有你的钱的人
I want the girl.
我要那个女孩
Where's Daddy?
爸爸在哪儿
He...
他..
had an accident.
发生了意外
He sent me.
他派我来的
Do you want your money or not?
你到底要不要你的钱
The girl got to this point alive.
这个女孩活着走到了这一步
But if you as much as sneeze
但如果你不经我
without my permission,
允许就打喷嚏,
that could be easily rectified.
那就很容易纠正了
-Got it. -Good.
-知道了 -很好
Now, see the locker behind you?
现在 看到你身后的储物柜了吗
Weapon and phone go in the locker,
武器和手机放在柜子里,
along with the clothes you're wearing.
还有你穿的衣服
Slam the door shut, and it'll lock.
关上门 它就会锁上
Go to the Westfield Mall across the street.
去街对面的韦斯特菲尔德购物中心
You, the suitcase, the new clothes
你 手提箱 新衣服
and the little girl's phone.
还有小女孩的手机
Seriously?
真的吗
Ten minutes.
十分钟
Hello, Sam.
你好 萨姆
Bonehead.
骨头
-Hey, Sam. -Sam.
- 嘿 山姆 - 萨姆
Boneheads.
骨头
-I really don't have time for this. -Nathan's worried about you.
-我真的没有时间了 -内森很担心你
Doesn't want you to do anything stupid.
不希望你做任何傻事
So why don't you hand over the suitcase,
你为什么不把手提箱交出来,
and nobody gets hurt.
而且没人会受伤
Go back to Nathan, tell him you tried, but I roughed you up.
回去找内森 告诉他你尽力了 但我对你动粗了
Ooh.
哦
You can beat each other up for added realism.
为了增加真实感 你们可以互相攻击
-That's funny. -What?
-真有趣 -什么?
No guns today?
今天不能带枪
Nathan doesn't want you hurt.
内森不想让你受伤
Not too badly, anyway.
反正不会太严重
Oh, that is so sweet.
真是太贴心了
I'll try not to kill you, too.
我会尽量不把你也杀了
♪ We can fight ♪
♪我们可以打
♪ Fight, fight ♪
♪打 打
♪ Fight, fight, fight ♪
♪打 打 打♪
Who the fuck is she?
她到底是谁？
♪ We can fight ♪
我们可以战斗
Ground floor. Video Beast.
一楼 录像 野兽
Cutting it close.
时间紧迫
I had a few hiccups.
我打了几个嗝
We saw what you did with those hiccups. How do we know you're not a cop?
-我们看到你打嗝的样子了 -我们怎么知道你不是警察
Can a cop do what I just did?
一个警察能做我刚才做的事吗?
I just want the girl.
我只想要那个女孩
Then we'll get along just fine.
然后我们就会相处得很好
There's a shopping cart behind you.
你后面有一辆购物车
Put the suitcase inside.
把手提箱放进去
Push the shopping cart towards us,
把购物车推向我们
and we'll push the girl cart towards you.
我们会把女孩车推向你
One.
一
Two.
二
Three.
三
It's okay. You're safe.
没事了 你安全了
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
We're all stinking rich, you magnificent bastards.
我们都非常富有 你们这些伟大的混蛋
Stop the fucking car.
他妈的停车
Holy fuck!
我操
You greedy traitor!
你这个贪婪的叛徒
No... no!
不... 不!
No, no, no!
不不不
Fuck.
操
Anything broken?
有没有骨折
-Are you bleeding -No.
-你在流血吗 -没有
Bleeding on the inside?
内出血
How can you tell?
你怎么知道
It's inside.
在里面
You're probably fine. Let's go.
你可能没事 我们走吧
Try to keep up.
尽量跟上
I see you morons have found my stash.
看来你们这些白痴找到了我的藏毒点
This is some good shit, doc.
这真是好东西 医生
You should be very proud of yourself.
你应该为自己感到骄傲
This is not a toy.
这不是玩具
It's for medicinal use only.
这只是医用的
So...
所以..
who fucked you up like this?
谁把你弄成这样的
A girl.
一个女孩
A girl made you look like you're from The Walking Dead?
一个女孩让你看起来像是《行尸走肉》里的
I've never felt pain like this before, doc.
我从来没有感到过这样的疼痛 医生
She got us good, doc. I...
她把我们害惨了 医生 我..
I don't think I'll ever walk again.
我想我再也不能走路了
There must be an epidemic,
肯定有传染病,
'cause I got a guy in the next room who's got similar symptoms.
因为隔壁有个人也有类似的症状
What do you mean?
什么意思
I mean...
我是说..
a girl fucked him up, too.
一个女孩也把他搞了
Keep talking, doc.
继续说 医生
You're bleeding.
你在流血
It's just a scratch.
只是擦伤而已
It can get infected.
它可能会被感染
Worms will get in there and lay eggs. Then they'll have to cut your arm off.
虫子会进入那里并产卵 然后他们就得把你的胳膊切下来
That's what they teach in school these days?
这就是他们现在在学校教的
Discovery Channel.
探索频道
Thank God we're going straight to the hospital.
谢天谢地我们要直接去医院
Is my daddy there?
我爸爸在吗
Yeah.
是的
Is that why he didn't come?
这就是他没来的原因
Is he sick?
他病了吗
He...
他..
It's okay.
没关系
You don't have to lie for him.
你不必为他撒谎
He never comes when he says he will.
他从来都是说来就来的
Here, just let me help you.
来 让我帮你
Thank you.
谢谢你
Sure.
当然
Are you sure it's her?
你确定是她吗
Yeah. She dropped off some guy she shot.
是的 她把一个被她打死的人送到这里
Said she's going to come back and pick him up later.
她说她一会儿会回来接他
And the money?
那钱呢
She had it last time we saw her.
我们上次见到她的时候她还带着呢
Then get it back.
然后把它拿回来
She's still getting the VIP treatment?
她还在享受 VIP 待遇吗
-Do whatever it takes. -Alright, alright, alright.
-不惜一切代价 -好吧好吧好吧
Now that's what I call a work benefit.
这就是我所说的工作福利
Just, uh, stay behind me, okay?
跟在我后面好吗
Come on.
来吧
I'll get the doctor.
我去叫医生
She's here.
她来了
Shot in the shoulder.
肩膀中枪
Maybe you should take your break now.
也许你该休息一下了
So. My payment?
那么 我的报酬呢
-Oh! -Shh.
-哦! -嘘
Transferred to your account.
转到你的账户上了
Now...
现在..
What's the plan, doc?
有什么计划 医生
Oh.
哦
Once I stick her with this, she'll start losing control of her arms.
一旦我把这个放在她身上 她就会开始失去对手臂的控制
After 60 seconds or so...
大约60秒后..
she's a sitting duck.
她就是个活靶子
What's wrong with you Let me do this right.
你怎么回事 让我来处理
It's just a scratch.
只是擦伤而已
Well, scratches get infected.
抓伤会感染的
That's how you lose an arm.
这就是你失去一只手臂的原因
Mm. Yeah, I heard.
嗯我听说了
What happened to him?
他怎么了
Someone shot him.
有人开枪打了他
I hear that's pretty lethal.
我听说那是相当致命的
Let's fix this.
让我们来解决这个问题
Don't. I'm good.
不用了 我没事
Trust me, you'll need this.
相信我 你会需要这个的
I said, I'm good.
我说 我很好
I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
对不起 我不是故意..
You motherfu...
你他妈的..
-Ah! -60 seconds!
-啊! -60秒
60 seconds!
60秒
60 seconds.
Oh, come on. Come on!
拜托 拜托
Listen, I need your help.
听着 我需要你的帮助
Some bad men are coming to hurt us.
一些坏人要来伤害我们
Those who killed my dad?
那些杀了我爸爸的人
I promise I'll explain, but right now I need your help, okay?
我保证我会解释的 但现在我需要你的帮助
-Okay. -Good.
好吗 好吧 很好
Grab the biggest knife.
拿起最大的刀
Careful of the sharp end.
小心锋利的一端
Okay...
好吧
Now grab the tape.
现在拿上胶带
Excellent. Tape it to my hand.
好极了 用胶带粘在我手上
36...
32...
Now tape the gun to my other hand.
现在把枪绑在我另一只手上
Careful. It's loaded.
小心 上膛了
15... 14...
Round two, bitch.
第二回合 贱人
Boneheads?
笨蛋
Better get ready!
最好做好准备!
Oh, thank God it's just you three.
谢天谢地只有你们三个
For a second there, I thought it was someone dangerous.
有那么一瞬间 我还以为是个危险人物
The only reason you're still alive is 'cause Nathan wanted it that way.
你还活着的唯一原因是因为 Nathan 希望这样
Now, take my finger and put it on the trigger.
现在 把我的手指放在扳机上
Well, it's over now.
现在都结束了
I'm going to tear you into little pieces.
我要把你撕成碎片
And I'm gonna love every second of it.
我会爱上每一分每一秒
Great. Hold that thought.
很好 等一下
I'll be right out.
我马上就出来
You're being very brave, Emily.
你很勇敢 艾米丽
I need you to do one last thing for me,
我需要你为我做最后一件事,
and then go and hide, okay?
然后躲起来 好吗
Okay.
好吧
Hey, Bonehead.
嘿 笨蛋
Emily.
艾米丽
I need you to come grab the phone.
我需要你过来拿电话
Come on.
来吧
It's okay. Just pick it up.
没关系 把它捡起来
You are a goddamn rock star.
你是个该死的摇滚明星
Put it on speaker.
打开扬声器
Someone better start talking.
最好有人开口说话
That was a...
那真是..
jerk move, sending the Three Stooges after me.
混蛋派三个臭皮匠来找我
You left us no choice, Sam.
你让我们别无选择 山姆
There's always a choice.
总是有选择的
Oh, well, then, we can still figure this out.
那我们还是可以解决这个问题的
Just bring the money back.
把钱拿回来就行了
It's gone. The suitcase was blown to 1000 pieces.
不见了 箱子被炸成了1000块
Oh.
哦
That's really unfortunate.
真是不幸
So now what?
那现在怎么办
Oh, you know the drill, Sam.
你知道规矩的 山姆
You're no longer under our protection.
你不再受我们保护了
In your little massacre earlier tonight,
在你今晚早些时候的小屠杀中,
you killed the wrong people.
你杀错人了
Including Jim McAlester's son.
包括 Jim McAlester 的儿子
But I was sent by you.
但我是你派来的
By The Firm.
是公司派来的
It doesn't matter.
这并不重要
This is business, Sam.
这是生意 山姆
And you landed on the wrong side of the balance sheet.
而你在资产负债表上的位置是错误的
So...
所以..
It needs to be rectified.
这需要加以纠正
How's this for business?
这样做生意怎么样
If I get out of this alive,
如果我能活着出去,
I'm coming for you.
我来找你了
All of you.
你们所有人
I would expect no less.
我也希望如此
Goodbye, Sam.
再见 萨姆
-Yes? -Mr. McAlester, this is Nathan.
-什么事 -麦卡莱斯特先生 我是内森
I'm the head of the HR department here at The Firm.
我是公司人力资源部的负责人
What do you want?
你想要什么
To prevent an all -out war between our two fine organizations,
为了防止我们两个组织之间的全面战争,
we would like to offer you the woman responsible for your loss.
我们想让你为你的损失负责
So you had nothing to do with this?
所以你和这件事没有关系
I can assure you, this is not how The Firm conducts its business, sir.
我可以向你保证 这不是本所的经营方式 先生
It was an unsolicited action by a very troubled individual.
这是一个心烦意乱的人主动提出的要求
Now, I'm sending you her last location.
现在我把她的最后位置发给你
I hope this is satisfactory, sir.
希望您满意 先生
For now.
目前而言
Take everybody.
带上所有人
Don't come back until it's done.
完事之后再回来
-It's a text message from Nathan. -What's it say?
- 这是内森的短信 -他说什么？
"I'm sorry, child. I can no longer protect you."
“对不起 孩子 我再也保护不了你了 ”
"I left you a package to help you survive the next few days."
“我给你留了一个包裹 帮你度过接下来的几天 ”
"Take it, and disappear."
“拿着它 然后消失 ”
Then there's an address.
还有一个地址
That's close by.
就在附近
What if it's a trap?
如果这是个陷阱呢
Can you press the button We're parked on minus two.
你能按一下按钮吗 我们停在负二号车位
Just remember, you were spared
记住 多亏了一个八岁的
thanks to an eight -year -old girl.
女孩 你才幸免于难
Eight and three quarters.
八又四分之三
Sorry.
对不起
Eight and three quarters.
八又四分之三
Are you a serial killer?
你是连环杀手吗
What?
什么
No... Where did you learn that expression?
不... 你从哪里学到这个表达?
-History Channel. -Well...
-历史频道  -嗯..
I am not a serial killer.
我不是连环杀手
But... you kill people?
但是... 你杀人
Yes.
是的
So that makes you a killer.
所以你是个杀手
And you've killed more than one.
你杀了不止一个人
That is serial.
这是连环杀人案
It's...
这是..
It's more complicated than that.
事情没那么简单
Serial killers are, uh, you know, mentally unstable.
连环杀手精神不稳定
They kill people out of a compulsive urge.
他们杀人是出于一种强迫性的冲动
So, why do you kill them?
那你为什么要杀他们
For money?
为了钱
Again, it's, uh...
再说一次
It's complicated.
这很复杂
Look, I'm going to need your help for a little longer.
听着 我需要你再帮我一会儿
Because your arms are still paralyzed?
因为你的手臂仍然瘫痪
Yes. After that, I'll get you to your mother.
是的 之后我会带你去找你妈妈
She left a long time ago.
她很久以前就离开了
-To your grandparents, then. -They're dead.
-那就给你的祖父母 -他们死了
Uncles Anything?
叔叔 什么都行
We'll figure it out, okay?
我们会想出办法的 好吗
Okay.
好吧
So, here's an unrelated question.
所以 这里有一个无关的问题
Do you know how to drive?
你会开车吗
Let's go over it one more time. Left.
我们再复习一遍 左边
Right.
对
Yes, I've got it already.
是的 我已经知道了
"D" is for drive. "R" is for reverse.
“ d”代表开车 “ r”代表倒车
And you get to do the easy part, stepping on the gas and breaks.
然后你开始做最简单的部分 踩油门然后刹车
Don't be a smart -ass. Turn the key.
别自作聪明了 转动钥匙
Put it in drive.
把它开到前进档
Let's go.
我们走
That's it. Straighten up.
就这样 站直了
I'm driving.
我来开车
Yes, you are.
是的 你是
Don't worry about the bullets.
别担心子弹
Reverse. Now.
倒车 现在
Hard left!
向左转
-Put it in drive. -Yeah.
-开车 -好的
That's it.
就是这样
Hard left.
向左急转
Go, go, go.
走走走
Damn it!
该死
Get ready. Hard left.
准备好 向左转
And another hard left.
再来一次左转
Shh.
嘘
Okay. Put it in reverse.
好的 倒车
Hard right!
向右急转
Put it in drive.
把它开到前进档
Hard left.
向左急转
Put it in reverse.
倒车
Okay, kill the lights!
好了 把灯关了
Okay, be quiet. Duck down.
好了 安静点 蹲下
That's it. Get down.
就是这样 趴下
Okay. Put it in drive...
好的 开车
and close your eyes.
闭上眼睛
Keep her straight.
让她保持直线
Keep it straight.
保持直线
Are your eyes still closed?
你的眼睛还闭着吗
-Yes. -Good girl.
-是的  -好姑娘
Put it in reverse.
倒车
Can I turn on the radio?
我可以打开收音机吗
Go nuts.
疯了吧
♪ Though this world's essentially ♪
♪虽然这个世界本质上是
♪ An absurd place to be living in ♪
♪一个荒谬的地方 生活在其中
♪ It doesn't call for bubble withdrawal ♪
♪它不需要泡泡般的撤退
♪ I've been told it's a fact of life ♪
♪有人告诉我这是生活的事实
♪ Though this world's essentially ♪
♪尽管这个世界本质上是
♪ An absurd place to be living in ♪
♪一个荒谬的地方生活在其中
♪ It doesn't call for bubble withdrawal ♪
♪它不需要泡沫撤退
Emily, doorbell.
艾米丽 门铃响了
Didn't I teach you to always guard your back?
我不是教过你要时刻保护自己吗
Hi, Mom.
嗨 妈妈
Hi.
嗨
Is this, um...
这是..
Am I a grandmother?
祖母吗
God, no.
当然不是
Hi. I'm Emily.
嗨 我是艾米丽
-I'm her apprentice. -What?
-我是她的学徒 -什么
Emily.
艾米丽
Come.
来吧
...the additional burden of needing to care
照顾她12个月大的女儿
for her twelve -month -old daughter.
的额外负担
It will be at least a year...
至少要一年..
That is a hell of a story.
真是个精彩的故事
Mm. Hell of a night.
糟糕的一晚
Um... Try wiggling your fingers.
试着动动你的手指
-Feeling should come back in no time. -Yeah, it's already working.
-感觉很快就会恢复的 -是啊 已经起作用了
Excellent.
好极了
You look really good. Are you eating well?
你看起来真不错 你吃得好吗?
Cut the crap, Ma.
别废话了 妈
Where have you been for the last 15 years?
过去15年你去哪儿了
Around.
在附近
Watching you.
看着你
Making sure you're safe.
确保你的安全
Great parenting.
伟大的父母
Glad to see you taking an interest in my career.
很高兴看到你对我的事业感兴趣
-I never wanted this life for you. -How's that working out for you?
-我从没想过让你过这样的生活 -你觉得怎么样
I wanted to stay with you and your aunts, but I couldn't.
我想和你还有你的阿姨们呆在一起 但是我不能
Why not?
为什么不呢
Because I fucked up.
因为我搞砸了
I fucked up.
我搞砸了
I was young when I had you.
我生你的时候很年轻
We left London, followed your father here. When he died...
我们离开伦敦跟着你父亲来到这里他死的时候..
When he was murdered.
当他被谋杀的时候
When he was murdered, you were a baby. I had nothing.
他被杀的时候你还是个婴儿我一无所有
No money, nowhere to go.
没有钱 无处可去
I knew Anna May from your dad's work.
我是从你爸爸的工作中认识安娜 · 梅的
She and the other aunts took us in.
她和其他姑妈收留了我们
The best years of my life.
那是我生命中最美好的时光
Me too.
我也是
Fast -forward twelve years, and I find out who shot your dad.
十二年过去了 我找到了枪杀你父亲的凶手
The Russians?
俄国人
The Russians from the diner?
餐馆里的俄罗斯人
Once I knew, I couldn't let him walk around enjoying life...
一旦我知道 我不能让他走来走去享受生活..
knowing what he did to us.
知道他对我们做了什么
But he was in bed with The Firm, so there was a price to pay.
但他和公司有关系 所以要付出代价
Once I killed him, there was a mark on my back.
一旦我杀了他 我的背上就有一个标记
I couldn't take you with me.
我不能带你走
I couldn't risk your life.
我不能拿你的生命冒险
So I made Nathan promise to keep you safe.
所以我让内森承诺保护你的安全
I guess that's over.
我想一切都结束了
There isn't a day that goes by I don't regret pulling that trigger.
没有一天我不后悔扣动了扳机
But back then, I couldn't help myself.
但当时 我情不自禁
I'm sorry.
对不起
Does the kid know about you and her dad?
-那孩子知道你和她爸爸的事吗
No.
-不知道
But she's smart.
但她很聪明
She'll figure it out.
她会想出办法的
What happens when she does?
如果她知道了会怎样？
I think there's a bad man outside.
我想外面有个坏人
We have to get out of here.
我们必须离开这里
-So, what's the plan -Can you press the lobby button?
计划是什么 你能按一下大厅的按钮吗
-What plan -Come on, you always have a plan.
什么计划 拜托你总是有计划的
A secret escape route A warehouse filled with guns?
一条秘密逃跑路线 一个装满枪支的仓库
I called us an Uber.
我给我们叫了一辆Uber
-Are you kidding me -No.
-你在开玩笑吗 -没有
An Uber. What the hell are you talking about?
一辆Uber 你到底在说什么？
I know you. You make plans.
我了解你 你有计划
And then you make plans to make other plans.
然后你制定计划 再制定其他计划
You're frothing at the mouth.
你在口沫横飞
It's unbecoming.
这是不合适的
Get them!
抓住他们
Don't feel bad.
别难过
Could happen to anyone.
任何人都可能发生这种事
My hand is still paralyzed.
我的手仍然瘫痪着
Yeah, course it is.
是的 当然是
-It is. -I know.
-是的 -我知道
Right. After you, ladies.
好吧女士们先请
Come on. Hurry up.
快点 快点
-Where does it go -Fucking Narnia.
-它通向哪里 -该死的纳尼亚
Go. In.
进去
-In! -Fine.
-进去! -好吧
-No plan, huh -Now is not the time.
-没有计划 -现在不是时候
Out of my way.
让开
-Need help, Ma -No, thank you.
-需要帮忙吗 妈 -不 谢谢
I'm quite capable...
我很有能力..
of disposing of one...
处理掉一个..
...idiotic grate.
...愚蠢的栅栏
That freezer is a mess. It's completely unacceptable.
那个冰箱一团糟 完全不能接受
-Come on. -Are you kidding me?
来吧 你在开玩笑吗
-We have to go. -Go where?
我们得走了 去哪里
Obviously your plan was to end up here.
显然你的计划就是在这里结束
-That was a long time ago. -Mom...
-那是很久以前的事了 -妈妈..
-I'm not going in there. -Mom, listen.
-我不进去 -妈妈听着
We need weapons and a car. We need a safe house!
我们需要武器和一辆车 我们需要一个安全屋
I'm not sure they'd let me in!
我不知道他们会不会让我进去
Only one way to find out.
只有一个办法能知道
Hey.
嘿
For the record, I still think this is a shit idea.
郑重声明 我仍然认为这是个糟糕的主意
Madeleine?
玛德琳
Girls, I think I see a ghost.
姑娘们 我想我看到了一个幽灵
-Hi, Madeleine. -Hi, Scarlet.
-你好 玛德琳 -你好 斯嘉丽
Florence.
佛罗伦萨
-Hi, Anna May. -No.
-嗨 安娜・梅 -不
No, no. You don't get to talk.
不 不 你没资格说话
Because you're a ghost, and ghosts can't talk.
因为你是个幽灵 而幽灵不能说话
You know how I know that?
你知道我怎么知道的吗
Can we do this later?
我们能晚点再谈吗?
Because if ghosts could talk,
因为如果鬼魂能说话,
they would say something before disappearing.
他们会在消失前说些什么
Or at least leave a note. But they can't.
或者至少留个便条 但他们不能
So, ipso facto, you're a ghost.
所以 事实上 你是一个幽灵
-I'm sorry. -Fuck you.
-对不起 -去你的
Language, Anna May. There's a child present.
注意语言 安娜 · 梅 有个孩子在场
Fine.
好吧
-Fudge you. -Fudge you.
- 欺负你 - 欺负你
Fudge you!
欺负你！
And why is there a toddler in our place of business?
为什么在我们的工作场所有一个蹒跚学步的孩子
The short version?
长话短说
Please.
求你了
Her father was killed and she has nowhere else to go.
她的父亲被杀了 她无处可去
I was downsized by The Firm,
我被公司裁员了,
and they fed me to McAlester's endless supply of thugs.
他们把我交给麦卡莱斯特无穷无尽的暴徒
And you decided to come here?
你决定来这里吗
Shall we return at a more convenient time?
我们可以在更方便的时间再来吗
Maybe you should.
也许你应该这么做
It seems like whenever you come here,
似乎每次你来这里
you bring a war with you.
你都会带来一场战争
Bring your problems...
带着你的问题...
We need to table this.
我们得把这事搁置一边
Seconded.
附议
Let's go down.
我们下去吧
Go and take Emily.
去把艾米丽带走
I'll buy us some time.
我会为我们争取一些时间
I think I should stay.
我想我应该留下来
No.
不
I screwed this up.
我搞砸了
I'll clean up my own mess.
我会自己收拾烂摊子
We'll meet at the diner once I've finished them off.
吃完饭我们在餐馆见
Go.
去吧
Please.
求你了
Come.
来吧
Are you sure I could use the target practice.
你确定吗 我可以用打靶练习
Mm -mm.
嗯嗯
Anna May was right.
安娜 · 梅是对的
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
我不该把你牵扯进来
I'm staying with you.
我要和你在一起
No. No, you're not.
不 不 你不可以
You're going to the basement, where it's safe.
你去地下室 那里很安全
But you need me. I'm your apprentice.
但你需要我 我是你的徒弟
Okay, listen, Emily.
好吧 听着 艾米丽
The bad men are coming. I really need you to go with my mom.
坏人来了 我真的需要你和我妈妈一起走
No! I want to stay with you.
不! 我想和你在一起
-You can't. -But why?
-你不能 -为什么
Because...
因为..
Because I killed your father.
因为我杀了你父亲
You're lying. You just want to get rid of me.
你在撒谎 你只是想摆脱我
Your dad, he, um...
你爸他..
He stole from some very bad people.
他从一些很坏的人那里偷东西
And they hired me.
他们雇佣了我
And I shot him.
然后我开枪打了他
Come on. Let's go.
来吧 我们走
I need weapons.
我需要武器
Try the self -help section.
试试自助栏目
-I have to help her. -You need my permission?
我必须帮助她 你需要我的许可吗
-I can't bail on her again. -Why You're good at it.
我不能再放她鸽子了 为什么 你很擅长这个
I'm sorry I couldn't give it up back then and just stay here with you.
对不起 我当时不能放弃 只是留在这里和你在一起
You're human.
你是人类
You screwed up.
你搞砸了
I can only imagine how painful it was leaving her behind.
我只能想象离开她是多么痛苦
Leaving us all behind.
把我们都抛在身后
But she grew up to be a fine woman.
但她长大了 成为一个优秀的女人
I never wanted this life for her.
我从没想过让她过这样的生活
Maybe it was meant to be.
也许这是命中注定的
Or maybe she wanted to be just like her mother.
或者她想像她妈妈一样
I missed you.
我想死你了
We kept these ladies for you.
我们为你保留了这些女士
Just meet us at the diner.
在餐厅等我们
Come back in one piece, okay?
完好无损地回来 好吗
Both of you.
你们两个
Motherfucker!
狗娘养的
Is anything broken?
有什么破损吗？
-Are you bleeding -I'm fine.
你在流血吗 -我没事
Bleeding on the inside?
内出血
The rest of them are coming.
剩下的人马上就来了
Would it kill you to say thank you?
说声谢谢会死吗
You can still go, Ma. I'll cover you.
你还是可以走的妈妈我会掩护你
And miss all the fun?
错过了所有的乐趣
Women Who Run with the Wolves.
与狼共舞的女人
-Awakening the Giant Within. -Ammo?
-唤醒内心的巨人 -弹药
How to Win Friends and Influence People.
如何赢得朋友和影响他人
You should've stayed away from this line of work.
你应该远离这一行的
Are you kidding, Ma?
你在开玩笑吗 妈
You left.
你离开了
Killing people was the only thing I knew how to do.
杀人是我唯一会做的事情
Okay, maybe it wasn't the best environment to raise a child in.
好吧 也许那不是抚养孩子的最好环境
You think?
你认为呢？
It made you who you are.
它造就了你
At least we can agree on that.
至少我们能在这点上达成一致
And you are a strong, smart, incredibly impressive young woman.
你是一个坚强 聪明 令人印象深刻的年轻女性
There's not a single person on earth I'd rather kill people with.
世界上没有一个人是我愿意和他一起杀人的
Thanks, Ma.
谢谢妈妈
You're so strong! You can't be 8 and three quarters.
你太强壮了! 你不可能是八又四分之三岁
I am.
是的
You sure you're not 28 and three quarters?
你确定你不是28又四分之三岁
Anna May, Madeleine. Come and see this.
安娜 · 梅 玛德琳 过来看看这个
Oh.
哦
We're not leaving.
我们不会离开的.
Scarlet's still a librarian, no matter if she's an asshole.
斯嘉丽还是图书管理员 不管她是不是个混蛋
-Language. -Right.
-注意语言 -好的
-So these... -Jerks.
-所以这些... -混蛋
...jerks up there
...上面的混蛋们
just made the biggest mistake of their lives.
刚刚犯下了他们人生中最大的错误
They stepped into our library and threatened our own flesh and blood.
他们闯进我们的图书馆 威胁我们的亲骨肉
They're not gonna push us around.
他们不会摆布我们的
They're not gonna scare us off. This ends now.
他们不会把我们吓跑的 这事到此为止
Madeleine, finish getting the van ready.
玛德琳 把车准备好
Florence, you and I are going up there to thin the herd.
弗洛伦斯 你和我去那里疏散畜群
We're gonna bring the sky down on their mother -fudging heads.
我们要把天打下来砸在他们的脑袋上
All in favor?
都同意吗？
-Aye. -Aye.
-赞成 -赞成
Aye.
赞成
Motion carried.
动议通过
You think you have a chance here?
你觉得你还有机会吗
I have an army.
我有一支军队
Oh, yeah Well, I've got my mom.
哦 是吗 我有我妈妈
I wish we had more time, Ma.
我希望我们有更多的时间 妈妈
It's quality, not quantity.
重要的是质量 不是数量
Chin up.
振作起来
Why don't you come out, and I'll put a bullet through your head?
你为什么不出来 我会一枪打爆你的头
Nice and quick.
动作快点
Why don't you go fudge yourself?
你为什么不自己去捏造事实
If you make me work for it, I'll shoot you in the stomach.
如果你逼我 我就开枪打你的肚子
Then we'll have some real fun together.
然后我们一起找点真正的乐子
Hey, dum -dums.
嘿 笨蛋们
Hey, idiots. Catch these.
白痴 抓住这个
Idiots to the left. Morons to the right.
左边是白痴 右边是白痴
The rest of you knuckleheads stay here and kill those two.
其他人呆在这里 杀了那两个人
Shh.
嘘
Put these on.
穿上这个
I'm gonna make a little noise,
我要制造点噪音,
so play it loud.
那就放大声点
Can you do that for me?
你能为我做到吗
♪ Oh come on, come on ♪
来吧来吧来吧
♪ Come on, come on ♪
来吧来吧
♪ Didn't I make you feel ♪
我是不是让你觉得
♪ Like you were the only man ♪
你是唯一的男人
♪ Yeah Didn't I give you nearly everything ♪
我不是把一切都给你了吗
♪ That a woman possibly can ♪
那是一个女人可能做到的
♪ Honey, you know I did ♪
亲爱的 你知道我做到了
♪ But each time I tell myself that I ♪
但每次我告诉自己
♪ Well, I think I've had enough But I'm gonna show you, baby ♪
我想我已经喝够了但我要让你看看 宝贝
♪ That a woman can be tough ♪
那个女人可以很坚强
♪ I want you to come on ♪
我要你跟我来
♪ Come on, come on ♪
来吧 来吧
♪ Come on and take it ♪
来吧 拿着它
♪ Take another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
Take another little piece of my heart Now baby
♪ Break it ♪
把它打破
♪ Break another little bit of my heart Now, darling ♪
♪再伤我一点点心现在 亲爱的♪
♪ Oh, have a ♪
哦 拥有一个
♪ Have another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
Have another little piece of my heart Now baby
♪ You know you've got it ♪
你知道你拥有它
♪ If it makes you feel good ♪
如果它让你感觉很好
Sam!
山姆！
Reload!
重新装弹
♪ I need you to come on ♪
我需要你过来
♪ Come on, come on, come on ♪
来吧 来吧 来吧
♪ Now take it ♪
现在拿着它
♪ Take another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
Take another little piece of my heart Now baby
♪ Oh, break it ♪
哦 打破它
♪ Break another little bit of my heart Now, darling ♪
♪再伤我一点点心现在 亲爱的♪
♪ Yeah, come on now Oh, have a ♪
来吧来吧来吧
♪ Have another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
Have another little piece of my heart Now baby
♪ You know you've got it ♪
♪你知道你已经
♪ Take it ♪
拥有它♪
♪ Take another little piece of my heart Now, baby ♪
♪拿起我的心现在
♪ Oh, take it ♪
宝贝♪噢 拿起它♪
♪ Take another little bit of my heart ♪
拿起我的心又一小块♪
♪ Have another little piece of my heart ♪
拥有我心中的另一小片
You've got something in your hair.
你头发里有东西
It's a tooth.
是一颗牙齿
Hey.
嘿
He...
他..
He took Emily.
他带走了艾米丽
I couldn't save her.
我救不了她
It's okay.
没关系
We'll get her back.
我们会把她救回来的
It was nice...
很不错..
having a kid in the library again.
又有孩子在图书馆了
Huh?
什么
"There is little joy in life for me"
“我的生命中没有什么快乐
"And little terror in the grave"
”“坟墓里也没有什么恐惧
"I've lived the parting hour to see"
“我活着离别的时刻就是为了看见”
"Of one I would have died to save"
“那个我愿意为之牺牲的人”
Well, that was exciting. Been a long time since I killed someone.
真令人兴奋我已经很久没杀人了
Let me talk to Emily.
让我和艾米丽谈谈
It's a real tragedy
干我们这行的可怜
what happens to poor orphans in our line of work, you know?
孤儿的遭遇真是悲剧 你知道吗
It's really quite sad.
这真的很令人难过
What do you want?
你想要什么
My uncle insists on meeting you.
我叔叔坚持要见你
He says, skinning you alive will let him
他说 活剥了你的皮会
work through his, uh, grief.
让他克服他的 呃 悲伤
That's not too much to ask, is it?
-这要求不过分吧
If I come to you,
如果我去找你,
Emily goes free.
艾米丽就能获得自由
And everyone else is off the table.
其他所有人都不在考虑之列
Okay, we have a deal.
好吧 我们成交
The diner.
餐馆
Can't wait.
等不及了
We gotta go.
我们得走了
You can't just hand yourself over to those animals.
你不能就这样把自己交给那些禽兽
They can't bring guns into the diner.
他们不能带枪进餐馆
-It's Emily's best chance. -It's a suicide mission.
-这是 Emily 最好的机会 -这是自杀任务
Well, someone else got a plan Hmm?
还有人有计划吗
I, uh... I don't right now, no.
我现在不知道
But it's you, Mom.
但那是你 妈妈
You always have a plan.
你总是有计划的
Sorry.
对不起
Then I guess this is goodbye.
那么我想这就是再见了
They're waiting for you, honey.
他们在等你 亲爱的
Thanks, Rose.
谢谢 罗斯
Did they hurt you?
他们伤害你了吗
It's been a long day.
真是漫长的一天
It's gonna be over soon, okay?
很快就结束了 好吗
Okay.
好吧
You're a special kid, Emily.
你是个特别的孩子 艾米丽
I wish I had more time to get to know you.
我希望我有更多的时间来了解你
I'm Jim.
我是吉姆
Samantha.
萨曼莎
You know, Samantha...
你知道 萨曼莎..
I've always considered myself a feminist.
我一直认为自己是个女权主义者
When my first daughter was born, I was over the moon.
当我的第一个女儿出生时 我欣喜若狂
Painted half the house pink.
把房子的一半漆成了粉红色
It was all unicorns and lollipops.
到处都是独角兽和棒棒糖
And my second daughter was born.
我的第二个女儿出生了
And the third and the fourth.
还有第三个和第四个
Girls...
姑娘们..
always whispering at the dining table.
总是在餐桌上窃窃私语
Always giggling in dark corners.
总是在黑暗的角落里咯咯笑
I love my girls.
我爱我的女儿们
But I don't understand them.
但是我不理解他们
Then my son was born.
然后我的儿子出生了
It was different.
这是不同的
Simple.
很简单
We understood each other.
我们互相理解
And I wasn't alone any more.
我不再是一个人了
I know...
我知道
it was just a job to you, and he was...
那只是你的工作 而他..
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
在错误的时间出现在错误的地点
None of that matters,
这些都不重要,
because you took him away from me.
因为你把他从我身边夺走了
I'm going to do terrible things to you, Samantha.
我要对你做可怕的事情 萨曼莎
You're going to suffer more than you thought even possible.
你会遭受比你想象中更多的痛苦
Because you have made me a stranger in my own home again.
因为你让我在自己家里又变成了一个陌生人
For what it's worth...
不管怎样..
I am very sorry about your son.
你儿子的事我很遗憾
Thank you, Samantha.
谢谢 萨曼莎
Just let the girl go.
让那个女孩走吧
Not yet.
还不行
We had a deal.
我们说好的
And I'm a man of my word.
我是个言出必行的人
I will set the girl free, unharmed.
我会放了那个女孩 毫发无伤
But only after she's watched what I do to you.
但只有在她看到我对你做了什么之后
Please.
求你了
Please, I...
求你了我..
I will do anything.
我愿意做任何事
Don't start begging yet.
先别乞求
There's plenty of time for that.
我们有的是时间
-Can I get you something -No, we're just fine.
-要喝点什么吗 -不用了 我们很好
Maybe some more coffee, or apple pie?
再来点咖啡 或者苹果派
If I have to tell you no again, there will be consequences.
如果我不得不再次拒绝你 后果会很严重
Hi, sweetheart.
嗨亲爱的
Hi, Mom.
嗨妈妈
Guess there was a plan, after all.
看来还是有计划的
Guess so.
我想是的
Why don't you take Emily out of here?
你为什么不带艾米丽离开这里
It's no place for a kid.
这里不适合孩子
Stay out of this, ladies.
别插手此事 女士们
It's not your fight.
这不是你的战斗
There's no more standing on the sidelines.
再也没有旁观者了
We all need to pick a side.
我们都需要选择一边
Right, ladies.
好了 女士们
♪ You must leave now ♪
你必须现在离开
♪ Take what you need You think will last ♪
♪带上你所需要的你认为会持续下去
♪ But whatever it is you think you need ♪
但是不管你认为你需要什么
♪ You better grab it fast ♪
你最好快点抓住它
♪ Yonder stands your orphan with his gun ♪
那边站着你的孤儿和他的枪
♪ Crying like a fire in the sun ♪
像阳光下的火焰一样哭泣
♪ Look out The saints are coming through ♪
小心圣徒们要过来了
♪ And it's all over now Baby Blue ♪
现在一切都结束了宝贝蓝色
♪ The highway is for gamblers You'd better use your sense ♪
♪公路是给赌徒的你最好用你的感觉♪
♪ Take whatever you've gathered up From coincidence ♪
把你收集到的东西从巧合中拿出来
♪ The empty -handed painter From your streets ♪
♪来自你街道的空手画家♪
♪ Is drawing crazy patterns On your sheets ♪
在你的床单上画着疯狂的图案
♪ The sky too now is folding up on you ♪
天空现在也折叠在你身上
♪ And it's all over now Baby Blue ♪
现在一切都结束了宝贝蓝色
♪ It's all over ♪
一切都结束了
♪ Baby Blue ♪
♪浅蓝色♪
♪ It's all over, baby ♪
一切都结束了
♪ Baby Blue ♪
宝贝
Emily.
艾米丽
I am so sorry I killed your father, Emily.
我很抱歉我杀了你父亲 艾米丽
If I could take it back...
如果我能收回..
I know.
我知道
But you tried to save him.
但你试图救他
Still.
不过
And you saved me.
你救了我
Thank you.
谢谢你
Besides... I know you just pulled the trigger.
而且... 我知道是你开的枪
I know there was someone else who told you what to do.
我知道还有其他人告诉你该怎么做
Who sent you to my father?
谁派你去见我父亲的
There's a group of men called The Firm.
有一帮人叫 "公司"
It's a... It's a girl scout.
是个... 是个女童子军
Get rid of her.
把她赶走
No, wait.
不 等等
They've been running things for a long, long time.
他们已经掌权很长很长时间了
They make all the rules and...
他们制定所有的规则..
change them when it fits their needs.
当符合他们的需要时 就改变他们
They think they're untouchable.
他们认为自己是不可触犯的
They think they can get away with anything.
他们认为他们可以逃避任何事情
But they won't, right?
但他们不会 对吧
No.
是的
They won't.
他们不会的
Not any more.
现在不是了
Well, well, well. What do we have here?
好吧 好吧 好吧 我们在这里有
I'm selling cookies.
什么 我在卖饼干
Oh, really Uh, where are they?
哦 真的吗 他们在哪里
You're the little girl that I've heard so much about, aren't you?
你就是那个久仰大名的小女孩吧
They think so little of me they sent a child to do their dirty work?
他们这么看不起我 竟然让一个孩子来干他们的脏活 坦白说
I'm insulted, frankly.
我觉得受到了侮辱
"Look into your heart"?
”审视你的内心”
Fuck me.
我操
Can you hear me?
你能听见我说话吗
Loud and clear.
声音大而清晰
We're both alive and well.
我们都活得好好的
That's the way it's gonna stay.
就这样吧
Come on, Sam. You know that's not up to me.
别这样 山姆 你知道这不是我能决定的
You get one chance to end this now.
你现在只有一次机会结束这一切
Years ago, my mom screwed up and pulled the wrong trigger.
几年前 我妈妈搞砸了 扣下了错误的扳机
I'm not making the same mistake.
我不会再犯同样的错误
That little girl in front of you will have a future.
你面前的那个小女孩会有前途的
Go back to the partners and tell them we know where they work,
回到合伙人那里告诉他们我们知道他们在哪工作,
where they live.
他们住的地方
We can kill them 100 times over without them ever seeing us coming.
我们可以杀死他们100多次 而他们根本看不到我们的到来
Tell them they were only spared
告诉他们是因为一个八岁的小女孩
because of an eight -year -old girl.
他们才幸免于难
Eight and three quarters.
八又四分之三
Sorry. Eight and three quarters.
对不起 八又四分之三
Got it?
明白了吗
Got it.
明白了
Now, close your eyes and count to ten.
现在 闭上眼睛 数到十
Slow.
慢点
One...
一..
two...
二..
three...
三..
four...
四..
five...
五..
six...
六..
seven...
七..
eight...
八..
nine...
九..
ten.
十
Can I drive?
我能开车吗
No.
不能
Can I turn on the radio, then?
那我可以打开收音机吗
Go nuts, baby girl.
疯狂吧 宝贝女儿
Right folks, time to hit the road.
好了 伙计们 该上路了
Take care, and see you on the other side.
保重 我们在另一边见
♪ Well I got us on a highway I got us in a car ♪
我把我们带上了高速公路我把我们带上了一辆车
♪ I got us going faster Than we've ever gone before ♪
我让我们比以前走得更快
♪ I got us on a highway I got us in a car ♪
我让我们上了高速公路我让我们上了一辆车
♪ I got us going faster Than we've ever gone before ♪
我让我们比以前走得更快
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last ♪
我知道这不会持续很久
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last
我知道它不会持续下去当我看
♪ When I see your eyes arrive ♪
到你的眼睛到达时
♪ They explode like two bugs on glass ♪
它们像玻璃上的两只虫子一样爆炸
♪ Far above the ocean Deep under the sea ♪
♪远在海洋之上深在海洋之下♪
♪ There's a river running dry 'Cos of you and me ♪
有一条河流因为你和我而干涸
♪ Far above the ocean Deep under the sea ♪
♪远在海洋之上深在海洋之下♪
♪ There's a river running dry 'Cos of you and me ♪
有一条河流因为你和我而干涸
♪ And I know It ain't gonna last ♪
我知道这不会持续很久
♪ It ain't gonna last ♪
它不会持续很久